I will have your life.
Hida Kizuna.
Try it if you can.
I knew you'd try to attack.
Kunoichi Renne
Record of banishing evil
Stop.
What a nice moan.
Do you think you'll... get away with this?
I wonder what'll happen.
Stop.
You won't get away.
S-Stop.
As if I'd stop now.
So soft.
I'm obsessed.
Does it feel good?
As if!
But you sound like you like it.
You can't escape by squirming around.
Seems like you're enjoying it.
Secret Technique:
Heart Hybrid
That is...
Secret Technique:
Heart Hybrid
I think you wanted this.
Secret Technique:
Heart Hybrid
Did you know why Kunoichi are called so?
Because of the female character having ku, no, and ichi.
No.
It's the amount of holes.
Eyes, two ears, nose, lips, belly button, anus and the urethra.
Also, the one thing a man doesn't have...
And the ninth means the kunoichi...
Just a speculation.
Stop that.
Didn't you want this?
No.
But... no...
Your body is more honest than you.
No...
It's fine.
Let me hear you moan.
Stop stop!
You seem to covet pleasure.
No way...
Seems like you really wanted it.
No!
Is that so?
You should just let yourself drown in pleasure.
Amazing! This is the Secret Technique: Heart Hybrid!?
What was I thinking?